When working across departments within your business,
在您的业务部门之间工作时
it's important to communicate regularly and clearly.
很重要的是定期沟通
Using the same language is a good way to make sure that all teams are on the same page.
使用相同的语言是确保所有团队都在同一页面上的好方法
It is imperative to be well-prepared when dealing with business objectives.
在处理业务目标时 必须做好充分准备
Other business units might wish to make more aggressive commitments to close more sales.
其他业务部门可能希望做出更积极的承诺 以关闭更多的销售
Be cautious and transparent.
谨慎和透明
Make sure the business understands what meeting
确保业务了解会议
higher commitments will cost in terms of both time and dollars.
更高的承诺在时间和金钱上都要付出代价
Service disruptions can be rare enough that
服务中断的情况非常罕见
how to recover can be forgotten and can be tricky.
如何恢复可以被遗忘 可以很棘手
Practicing recovery operations is key to doing them well,
进行恢复操作是做好这些工作的关键
which in turn is key to keeping relationships
这反过来也是保持关系的关键
on solid footing with your peers in other parts of the business.
与其他业务部门的同行建立稳固的基础
We'll be taking a look at recovery metrics and
我们将会查看恢复度量值和
planning that tie in closely with business needs.
与业务需求紧密联系